[id: lacvuqqb]
[ar:L'Arc~en~Ciel]
[ti:THE BLACK ROSE]
[al:KISS]
[by:Bebek]
[00:01.21]L'Arc~en~Ciel - THE BLACK ROSE
[00:13.85]-= Bebek =-
[00:17.22][00:32.65][00:50.58][01:15.08][01:33.83][01:53.81][02:17.76][02:48.35][03:17.66]
[00:21.42]Renzoku suru jiken ni kanrenshi
[00:26.79]nokosarete ita SAIN
[00:29.28]shin'i wa?
[00:32.98]It is the black rose azawarau
[00:42.42]Scattered roses abakidaze
[00:50.98][01:54.14][02:48.56]Chase faster.
[00:53.76][01:56.76]shinayaka ni tesuri nukete me o kuremasu
[01:00.84][02:04.15][02:58.48]End that bastard.
[01:03.90][02:06.88]bara o maita no wa dare?
[01:08.88][02:11.99]There’s no time, but who’s the next target?
[01:24.92]Kanjiru hou e shinkei o togarase
[01:29.80]konzen to shita jouhou no mouten e
[01:35.87]Smell of the black rose sasoidashi
[01:45.97]Scattered roses oitsumeru
[02:30.07]It is the black rose sakihokoru
[02:39.75]Scattered roses azawarau
[02:51.11]abakidashita shunkan ni me o fusagare
[03:01.32]yami ni hisomu no wa dare?
[03:06.32]ashimoto ni chirabaru the black roses,
[03:13.93]But who’s the next target?
[03:16.82]…Me!?
